[music]
[screaming] Hey hey hey who is this other man
?  Hey, he is the nephew of Sheela aunty from next door, he has come to
visit.   Move away.
Hey, give it to me, I will play a little.
Papa friend.  Hey, both of you play together.  See,
by doing this the steering rotates.
Tire.
Oh yes, that's it.  And by doing this the car moves forward and
backward.
Bring it and show it.  Both of them are playing together, right?  Come,
hold my hand.
Meaning, this snake should become a snake.
Why is she so scared like this?  Wave Yeeee.
Son Loki, it's time for school, come.
Yes, Papa came.   Okay,
I am going.  Now you are gone son.  Now
you are gone and see.  I will show you your place.
Today [music] is Saturday.  Today I
will play the whole night.
What happened?  Why is Sheela Aunty's house locked
?
Hey, that kid had come, everyone went to his house.